(Raj:)It wasn't easy.
(Amy:)They're gonna have sex
before Sheldon and I do. I knew it.
(Sheldon:)-Arthur.
-Hi, Sheldon.
(Sheldon:)I'm surprised to see you here.
(Arthur:)Yeah, me, too.
(Arthur:)Somewhere around the third floor,
I began to see a white light.
(Sheldon:)I'll get Leonard.
(Sheldon:)No, no, no, I'm...
I'm hereto see you.
(Sheldon:)If you're hoping to get in touch
with Bill Nye, I can't help you.
(Sheldon:)I've been informed that he's now
Bill Nye the Restraining Order Guy.
No, I'm... I was thinking,
if it isn't too much trouble,
(Arthur:)I'd like to get your opinion
about my paper.
(Sheldon:)Thank you. It would be an honour.
Oh, great.
Well, actually, I don't need that.
(Sheldon:)I hacked into your e-mail
account and read it.
(Arthur:)And... what did you think?